Guide to the Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, Records SC0541
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2003-241
  - Additional Records, Subseries 2
    - Service-Learning Syllabi; Constructing HIV/AIDS: The Epidemic’s Second Decade; Prof. R. Linden (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Service-Learning Syllabi; GSB R393: Working with Diversity: Opportunities and Obstacles; Prof. D. Meyerson (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Service-Learning Syllabi; Public Policy 180: Washington, D.C.: Players and Issues; Prof. C. Milton (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Service-Learning Syllabi; Psychology 180A: Project S.A.V.E.; Prof. Pertofsky (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Service-Learning Syllabi; Anthro. 182A: Zuni; Prof. J. Rick (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Service-Learning Syllabi; Comm. 114: Introduction to the Moving Image; Prof. K. Samuelson (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Service-Learning Syllabi; Psychology 186: Social Psychology of Social Problems: A Focus on Chicanos; Prof. F. Soriano (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Service-Learning Syllabi; American Studies 120 / Urban Studies 150: Process & Practice of Community Service; Prof. J. Cohen & T. Stanton (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Haas Center Course: Motivated to Serve, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Haas Center Course: Motivated to Serve, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Haas Center Course: Motivated to Serve; Readings, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Course Reader: American Studies 120 / Urban Studies 120: Process and Practice of Community Service; Prof. T. Stanton, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Course Reader: Public Policy 179A, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2006-301
  - Files from Floppy Discs, Subseries 1
    - Visiting Mentor Program: Everything About What’s Behind It and How It Works, 1999 Nov (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Visiting Mentors, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Visiting Menors -- Alumni Center, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Visiting Mentors -- David Hilfiker, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Marti Leicester, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Nomination, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Overviews, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Selection Process, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Stuart Burden, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Suzan Shown Harjo, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Tony Massengale, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Chris Avery, circa 2000 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Linda Wong, 1997 winter (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Visiting Mentor, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Lorne Needle, 1998 spring (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Paul Loeb, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Visiting Mentors -- Sarah von der Lippe, 1999 spring (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Stanford Leaders for Public Service 2001-2002 Syllabus (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Youth and Schools Program Files, Subseries 2
    Files in this subseries are likely from Janyce Prothro (Ravenswood Reads Program Coordinator).
    - Ravenswood Tutor Manuals, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - How to survive at Haas, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Corp. for Nationall Service, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Youth and Education Series, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Youth/Schools Programs: Evaluations/Reports, 1993, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Ravenswood Marketing Plan, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Good Deeds Workshop, 1996 Oct (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Reading One-To-One, 1998-2000 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Reading One-To-One, 1997-1999 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Ravenswood Reads Quarterly Evaluations, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Haas Evaluation Process, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Ravenswood Tutor Packet, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Youth and Schools Program Files, Subseries 3
    Files in this subseries are likely from Anne Takemoto (School Programs Coordinator and Ravenswood Stanford Tutoring Program Coordinator).
    - Schools Programs History, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - School Support Programs Assessment Report, 1993 Jun (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Haas Organizational/Policy History, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Stanford-Costano Partnership, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - East Palo Alto, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Youth/Education Programs, 1990s (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Tutoring Times, 1987-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - America Reads Weekly Reflections, 1998 spring (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Schools Visionary Ideas, 1992-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Youth and Schools Program Files, Subseries 4
    Files in this subseries are likely from Jacqueline Mohalley (Volunteer Coordinator for School Programs).
    - Volunteer Coordinator, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Youth and Schools Program Files, Subseries 5
    The source of these files is unknown.
    - School Programs, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - School Programs II, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - School Programs I, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - ED 100X, 1996-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Service-Learning Courses, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Articles, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - SCALE, circa 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Bay Area Community Outreach Partnership Center Materials, Subseries 6
    - Hartung/Community Outreach Partnership Center Info, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Community Outreach Partnership Center Renewal, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Bay Area Community Outreach Partnership Center, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Bay Area Community Outreach Partnership Center Advisory Bd., 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Community Outreach Partnership Center/EPA Conference, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Community Outreach Partnership Center Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Bay Area Community Outreach Partnership Center: HUD Grant Final Report, 1998 Feb (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - East Palo Alto Community Conference, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - HUD Faculty Group, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Final Report for HUD Community Outreach Partnership Centers, circa 1997 Jun (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - HUD Planning, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - OEPA-NII, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Service Learning 2000 Center Materials, Subseries 7
    - S/L 2000, 1993-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - School of Education, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Additional Records, Subseries 8
    - Faculty Outreach, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Odyssey Clearinghouse, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Haas Unifying Board 1999-2000 Report (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Haas Public Service Career Opportunities, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - BIRC, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - UCT-CHESP Delegation, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - UCT-CHESP, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Student Fellowship Programs Early Visions, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Student Organizations, Subseries 9
    - Alternative Spring Breaks, 1987-1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Costano-Stanford Partnership, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Democratic Partners, 2000 Apr (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - EPATT -- Youth Tennis Foundation of Northern California, 1994-1996 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Education Studies Program, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Health Corps, 1997 Apr (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Homeless Programs at Stanford, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Night Outreach, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - PASU -- Filipino-American, 1996-1999 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Ravenswood Stanford Tutoring Program, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - SAY, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - SEAC/SEAS, 1995-2001 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - SEPO, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Stanford Homeless Action Coalition, 1993-1997 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - SIDO, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - SIG, 1987-2000 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Stanford in Washington, 1992-1993, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - SLAC, 1999 Apr (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - SMUN, 1996-1997 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - SPOON, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Stanford Volunteer Network, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - SCHOOLS -- TEAM, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Tet Ansam, 1997 Apr (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Publications, Subseries 10
    - Annual Report, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1998-1999, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Since 1891… Growing the Public Service University, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - East Palo Alto Resource Directory, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Community Profile: East Palo Alto, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Haas Fliers, Brochures, 2003-2004 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Haas Programs/Organizational Summary Info, 2004-2005 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - 2003-2005 Biennial Report Source Book, 2006 Aug (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Scholarship for Social Change (PSSP First 10 Years), 1995-2005 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Gardner Fellowships, 1996-2005 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Profiles in Service, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Public Service Education at Stanford: The Haas Center’s First Twenty Years, 2005 Dec (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Savitha Moorthy (Stanford/Ravenswood Partnership Director) Files, Subseries 11
    - ED 105: American Education and Public Policies, 1992 fall (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Collaborative Tutor Training Project Year End Report, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - PSYCH 186/ED 186/CHICANST 108: Social psychology of Social Problems – "Under Pressure: Survey of Social Issues in Latino Communities", 1993 Fall (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - School Support Programs Assessment Report, 1993 Jun (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - PSYCH 186: Social Psychology of Social Problems, 1993 Apr (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Ravenswood Brochure, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Tutor Resource Manual, 1989 winter (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - ¡Expresion!, 1994 spring (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - VOICES: Stories from Mrs. Morrison’s 6th grade class, 1990 Jun (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Bay Area Tutoring Conference, 1989 Mar (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Pipeline Programs for Minority Students, 1996 Jan (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Suzanne Abel (Associate Director for External Relations / Former Director of Development and External Relations) Files, Subseries 12
    - Ravenswood Tennis Program Overview, circa 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Clippings, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - You Can Make a Difference Brochure, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Haas Opening Program, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Spirituality and Service Fellowship, undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Audiovisual Materials, Subseries 13
    - Embrace the Future: Ravenswood School District’s 8th Grade Graduation [VHS tape], 1996 Jun 14 (Box 6)
    - Five Miles to Next Service: RSTP and the Ravenswood School District [VHS tape] (Box 6)
    - Andy and Steph [audio cassette], 1995 May 18 (Box 6)
    - Copy of Andy and Stephanie interviews [audio cassette] (Box 6)
    - Dr. David Hilfiker M.D. [audio cassette], 1995 May 17 (Box 6)
    - Jason/Eddie You Can Make a Difference review, fall quarter [audio cassette], 1993 Jan 4 (Box 6)
    - You Can Make a Difference evaluations [audio cassette] 1993 Dec 6 and 1994 Mar 1 (Box 6)
    - You Can Make a Difference evaluation [audio cassette], 1993 May 13 and 20 (Box 6)
    - Joseph's House NPR "All Things Considered," David Hilfiker [audio cassette], 1995 Jan 8 (Box 6)
    - History of Haas Interview Jeremy Cohen and Catherine Jordan [audio cassette], 1994 May (Box 6)
    - Interview with Diane Coward [audio cassette], 1994 May 19 (Box 6)
    - History of Haas Discussion: Lucie, Sue, Jackie, Lissa [audio cassette], 1994 spring (Box 6)
    - History of Haas Discussion: Tim, Jeanne, Jackie, Lissa [audio cassette], 1994 spring (Box 6)
  - Files on Service-learning: A Movement's Pioneers Reflect on Its Origins, Practice, and Future by Timothy K. Stanton, Dwight E. Giles, Jr., and Nadinne I. Cruz., Subseries 14
    - Service-Learning: A Movement’s Pioneers Reflect on its Origins, Practice, and Future (Box 7)
    - Untitled, 1996-1998 (Box 7)
    - "Napkin" seminar, 1981-1996 (Box 7)
    - Service Learning Institute Program Review Portfolio Appendix, 2000 Nov (Box 7)
    - Summer Institute on Service-Learning in Health Professions Education, 1996 Jun-Jul (Box 8)
    - Service-Learning History Project, 1995-1996 (Box 8)
    - Stanford Summer Institute on Service-Learning, 1993-1995 (Box 8)
  - Posters, Subseries 15
    - Celebrating 20 Years of Service, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Public Service Center (pre-1990) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Untitled picture of a student group’s work at Lytton Gardens (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Untitled picture of a student group’s work at Lytton Gardens (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Untitled picture of event from early in Haas history; people in picture include Melissa Auchard, Sarah Von der Lippe (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Untitled picture of Bike-Aid (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Untitled; probably a picture of a one-day service event (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Untitled; probably a picture of a one-day service event (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Untitled; picture relates to You Can Make a Difference
    - Untitled; unknown event, one of the people pictured is Liz Erlich
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2007-247
  - Haas-Produced/Related General EPA Background, 1984, 1995-98 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Art inspired by OEPA participants/EPA residents (IDA), winter 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - OEPA-NII [One East Palo Alto Neighborhood Improvement Initiative] Tracking System 9/00-2/01 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - OEPA-NII Community Plan 6/26/00 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - OEPA-NII Community Information Packets 3/00, 7/00 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - OEPA-NII Resource Lists 4/25/00 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ravenswood Reads Tutoring Guide 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ravenswood TC/TA Responsibilities 5/25/05 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ravenswood Flyer fall 2004 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Original Brochures (Ravenswood), 2000-2004 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Upward Bound Newsletter Winter 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - LEAP (Leadership and Education through Adventure-based Programming) 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - LEAP 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - LEAP 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Upward Bound Student Roster 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Upward Bound Tutor Handbook 1994-95 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Upward Bound chron files 1994-95 June-September (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Upward Bound chron files 1994 Oct-Dec (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Upward Bound chron files 1995 Jan-March (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Upward Bound chron files 1995 April-May (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Upward Bound chron files 1995 June-July (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Upward Bound chron files 1995 Aug-Dec (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Upward Bound tutor handbook 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Upward Bound student handbooks 1995-96 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Upward Bound chon files 1996 Jan-May (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Upward Bound chon files 1996 June-Dec (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Upward Bound chon files 1997 Jan-May (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Upward Bound chon files 1997 June -1998 May (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Upward Bound chon files 1998 June-1999 May (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Upward Bound chon files 1999 June-2000 May (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Upward Bound Grant Proposal 2000-2005 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Suzette De Grange, correspondence September 1998 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Reports and evaluations, including budget application 1998 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Photographs of Upward Bound participants (students and some tutors) [untitled-dark brownish gray binder] 1997-99 and undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Upward Bound Summer 1996 Slideshow slides, 1992 -99 and undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Slides [untitled-marbled teal cardboard binder] 1994-98 and undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Slides [untitled-white binder], 2001 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Photographs; [untitled-red binder], 1989-91 and undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Upward Bound photographs and negatives, 7/03 and undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - UB Graduation, photographs and negatives, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - UB Graduation, photographs and negatives, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Upward Bound photographs, undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Oversize Photos (3 guys scaling a wall; 2 Band members with hospital patient; guy in Stanford sweatshirt with kid; female student at Haas Center) (Box 6)
  - Oversize posters: (2nd Annual Conference on Homelessness, 1989?; Nurturing Our Children, April 29, 1995; Cities in Crisis, Feb. 2, 1994; Deciding Our Environmental Future, Jan. 1989; Private Initiatives and Public Responsibilities, Feb. 22, 1986; and 4 undated ones on the Center and its programs) (Box 6)
  - Oversize sign boards from Haas Center Groundbreaking 1992 with signatures (Box 6)
  - Posters: A Century of Service / Celebrating Our Commitment Sept. 29, 1991; Conference on Hunger April 8-13, 1985
  - Display on Public Service Scholars (photos of 9 students with information on their projects)
  - Upward Bound Alumni Files (restricted files) (Box 7)
- Jeanne Halleck Files, Accession ARCH-2007-248
  - Stanford in Washington Files, Subseries 1
    - Stanford in Washington Advisory Committee 1986-1988 (Program Committee) (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Early Stanford in Washington Program Brochure (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Stanford in Washington Council 1994-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Stanford in Washington Council 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 4-5)
    - Stanford in Washington Council 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Stanford in Washington Council 1993- (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Stanford in Washington Council, Halleck File (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 1988 Dedication Party for Stanford in Washington (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
    - D.C. Dedication Program 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Armin Rosencranz Winter 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Bruce Owen (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - David Kennedy Fall 1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Tom Campbell Spring/Fall 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Roger Noll Fall 1995/Spring 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Jeremy Bulow Stanford in Washington Winter 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Thomas Moore Spring 1995 VFM (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Jerry Dorfman, Stanford in Washington Fall 1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - David Tyack and Elisabeth Hansot, Stanford in Washington Spring 1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Bob Augsburger, Stanford in Washington Winter 1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - John Wirth, Stanford in Washington Fall 1993 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Donald Kennedy, Stanford in Washington Winter 1993 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Tom McBride, Stanford in Washington Fall 1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Larry Cuban, Stanford in Washington Spring 1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Al Camarillo, Stanford in Washington Fall 1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Robert Crandel, Stanford in Washington Spring 1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Keith Krehbiel, Stanford in Washington Spring 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Michael Kirst, Stanford in Washington Fall 1990 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Gene Webb, Stanford in Washington Spring 1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - David Danelski, Stanford in Washington Spring 1989 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - James Risser, Stanford in Washington Fall 1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Fundraising 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Fundraising 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Fundraising 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Fundraising 1992 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Haas Fundraising/Friends of Stanford in Washington (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Stanford in Washington fund raising and budget (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Stanford in Washington fundraising (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Stanford in Washington fundraising – Most Recent (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Index of Stanford in Washington-Related Correspondence, Articles, Reports, Memoranda at Washington Campus, 1983-1987 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Stanford in Washington Planning/Set-up, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Stanford in Washington and University Budget Cuts, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Stanford in Washington – Rosse Options – 1989 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Stanford in Washington Budget 1993-94 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Stanford in Washington Tutorial Guidelines (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Stanford in Washington Budget (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Stanford in Washington -- Letters from Charles Ludlam (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Letters of Appreciation 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, Status Reports, and Advisory Board, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Director’s Correspondence 1991-1992 (Outgoing) (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, Stanford in Washington fundraising, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Director Search 1987 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - 1993 Danielski Farewell Reception at Stanford (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Director Search 1987 (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - D.C. Campus Search Committee 1986-1987, undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - D.C. Director Search Halleck File 1987 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Stanford in Washington Director Vacancy Announcement 1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Stanford in Washington director search, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Stanford in Washington Director Search Halleck File, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Stanford in Washington Director Searches Halleck File, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Stanford in Washington Program and Students/Staff Spring 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Stanford in Washington Evaluation Halleck File 1989-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Stanford in Washington Evaluation, 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Stanford in Washington Facilities Committee 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 2661 Connecticut Ave. Facility 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Facility Search 1986 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
    - Early Stanford in Washington Program Planning/Proposals, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Planning Committee Report May 1986 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Internship Program 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Licensure Approval 1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Washington Program Licensing, 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Washington Program Accreditation, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Catherine Milton’s Courses 1985 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Meeting re: Haas programs, particularly Stanford in Washington, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Programs in Washington 1989-1990 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Cornell -- D.C. 1983 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Program Development, Stanford in Washington, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
    - Program Development, Stanford in Washington, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Stanford in Washington 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Stanford in Washington 1995-1996 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Stanford in Washington Administration, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Proposals for "Washington Campus" 1984 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Proposal for Pilot Program 1985 (Correspondence, drafts, notes) (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Pilot Program 1985 -- Planning Committee (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - D.C. Campus – Proposals, Notes, Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Stanford in Washington Photos (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Stanford in Washington Clippings, 1993, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Clippings, 1986-1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Stanford in Washington Brochures, 2002, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Stanford in Washington Advertising/Promotional Material, 1987-1992 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Stanford in Washington Furnishings and Decorations (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Stanford in Washington Miscellaneous Notes and Memos, 1987-2004 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Stanford in Washington Committee Membership Lists, 1987, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Stanford in Washington Miscellaneous Memos Halleck file, 1987-1994 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Stanford in Washington Reporting Protocol, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Faculty Member in Residence, 1988-1993 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Stanford in Washington Program Committee Halleck File, 1987-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Haas Center General Files, Subseries 2
    - Haas -- Strategic Planning, circa 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Public Service Poster, circa 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Public Service Center Annual Report -- Drafts/Correspondence, 1984-1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Graduation 1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Public Service Center Brochures (Box 3, Folder 7)